Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence, 1977-1999; MS2040 Series 2
  - Author Correspondence, Frank Gatling, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Chasen Gaver, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Meghan Gehman, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Joanne Gelles, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Katy Gerhard, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Amy Gerstler, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Gess, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Daniela Gioseffi, n.d., undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Gabriele Glang, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Jesse Glass, Jr., 1978-1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Loss Glazier, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Edward S. Gold, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Barbara Goldberg, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Ivy Goldman, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Laurence Gonzales, 1984-1990 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Jaimy Gordon, 1980-1990 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, L. Suzanne Gordon, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Pamela Gordon, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Josh Gosciak, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Gossling, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Paul Grant, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Bob Grey, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Grayson, 1979-1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Grayson, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Grayson, 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Gregory, 1983-1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, C. Roger Greenwald, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, John Greenya, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, David Greisman, 1977-1990 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Sy Gresser, 1983-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Patricia Griffith, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Dave Griffiths, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Paul Grillo, 1978-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Todd Grimson, 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Andrew J. Grossman, 1984-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Gubernat, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Herb Guggenheim, 1977-1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Carolyn Guss, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Carolyn Guss, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, David Guy, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Hairing, 1980-1989 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Karla Hammond, 1977-1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Cathryn Hankla, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Hankla, 1977-1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Kate Hansen, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Johnny Hartner, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Hathaway, 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Haynes, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Hazuka, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Head, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Mike Hemmingson, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Essex Hemphill, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Judith Hemschemeyer, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Lisa Herskovitz, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, David Hickman, n.d., undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Casey Hill, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Nigel Hinshelwood, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Rolaine Hochstein, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Ed Hogan, 1978-1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Bill Holland, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Rochelle Holt, 1978-1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Lucy Honig, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Doug Hornig, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Horovitz, 1978-1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Paul House, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Justice Howard, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, William D. Hunt, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Kathleen Ingram, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence,Inman, Will, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Reuben M Jackson, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Lucky Jacobs, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Janisse, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Phil Jason, 1984-1986 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Wolfgang Jasper, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Lane Jennings, 1979-1988 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Deborah Jensen, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Curt Johnson, 1978-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Dan Johnson, 1976-1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, E.W. Johnson (Wotring), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Steven Johnson, n.d., undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Jones, 1982-1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Beth Joselow, 1981-1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Rodger Kamanetz, 1982-1988 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Rod Kane, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Ed Kaplan, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Kates, 1982-1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Ruth Moon Kempler, 1982-1989 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom Kennedy, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe Keppler, 1982-1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Jascha Kessler, 1982-1987 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Mike and Kathleen Kettner, 1983-1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Pat Kenning, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Kerry Shawn Keys, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Crad Kilodney, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Art Kimball, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Kathryn King, 1978-1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard King, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Wayne Kline, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Grant Kornberg, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Richard Kostelanetz, 1978-1986 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Dick Krawiec, n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Diane Kruchkow, 1981-1988 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, James Krusoe, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Roz Kuehn, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Frances Kuffel, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Mocha Laget, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Gary Lagier and "Literary Monitor", 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Christine Lahey Dolega, 1977-1985 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Paul Lake, n.d., undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Jay Landesman, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Lark, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Mariane LaRoche, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Sarah E. Lauzen, 1984-1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Kevin Lavey, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Paul Lawson, 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Lax, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Merrill Leffler, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Jessie Lendennie, 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Patricia Lesko, n.d., undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Debbie Levin, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Bill Levy, 1983-1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, James Liddy, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Lyn Lifshin, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Gary Ligi, 1984-1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Gerald Locklin, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Jonathan London, 1983-1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Judy Lopatin, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Rick Lopez, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Katharine Lorr, 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Bret Lott, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Clarinda Harriss Lott, 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Yann Lovelock, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Mark Lowe, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Rupert Loydell, 1984-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Dennis Lynds, 1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, George Lynn, 1974-1984 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Ed Lynskey, 1978-1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Myron Lysenko, 1983-1989 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter Lyssiotis, 1980-1986 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, David McAleavey, 1978-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Linda McCloud, 1978-1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Jean McGarry, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, G.J. McFarlane, 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Tom McGonigle, 1983-1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Erin McGraw, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Lou McKee, 1982-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Pat and Andrea McKinnon, 1984-1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Ann L. McLaughlin, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Sam McMillan, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Bruce McPherson, 1977-1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary MacArthur, 1977-1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Mackey, 1982-1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, James Magorian, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Robin Magowan, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, James Maher, 1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Kathleen Maher, 1982-1988 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Jim Mahoney, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Malinowitz, 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Bill Manhire, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Chris Mansell, 1981-1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Maura Manta, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Martone, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe Marusiak, 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Al Masarik, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Lois Mathieu, 1982-1986 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Cris Mazza, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Pablo Medina, 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Mark Melnicove, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Ann Menebroker, 1977-1983 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Douglas Messerli, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Terri Merz, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Author Correspondence, Greg Metras, 1980-1985 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Author Correspondence, William Meyer, n.d., undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Author Correspondence, D. Edmond Miller, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, E. Ethelbert Miller, 1978-1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeffrey Miller, 1976-1985 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Katherine T. Miller, 1986-1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Warren C. Miller, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, David Mincker, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Mike Miskowski, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, George Montgomery, n.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Glenn Moomau, 1984-1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Charley Moon (Mitcherson), 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Dave Moore, 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Elizabeth Moore, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Steven Moore, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Todd Moore, 1982-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Ruth Moose, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Sharon Morgenthaler, 1984-1989 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Dave Morice, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael Morrissey, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter Mortimer, 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Thylias Moss, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Andrew Mossin, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Doris Mozer, n.d., undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Judy L. Mudfoot, 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Anton Mueller, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Marnie Mueller, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Doug Mumm, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Fred Muratori, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Liz Murawski, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, George Murphy, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Robbie Murphy, 1984-1986 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, George Myers, Jr., 1978-1990 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Larry Navat, 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Ben Neihart, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Antonya Nelson, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Sandra Nelson, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Peter F. Neumeyer, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Sasha Newborn, 1978-1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Dawn Newton, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, David Nicholson, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, A.L. Nielson, 1979-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Ann Nietzke, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Kurt Nimmo, 1979-1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Damon Norko, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Naomi Shihab Nye, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Desmond O'Brien, 1976-1985 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, John O'Brien, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Barry Donohue, 1983-1987 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Michael O'Leary, 1982-1990 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Kirby Olson, 1981-1984 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Catherine O'Neill, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Greg Orfalea, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Sibbie O'Sullivan, 1982-1987 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Gil Ott, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Jane Overall, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Michelle Parkerson, n.d., undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Anselm Parlatore, 1983-1989 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Linda Pastan, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Noel Peattie, 1982-1989 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Pat Pepper, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Simon Perchik, 1981-1988 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, David Perkins, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Bob Peters, 1980-1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Ruth Pettus, n.d., undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, W.T. Pfefferle, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, James Phillips, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Constance Pierce, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Leslie Pietrzyk, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, David Plumb, 1981-1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Charles Plymell, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, Lily Pond, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Bern Porter, n.d., undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Jacklyn Potter, 1982-1989 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Charles Potts, 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Lee W. Potts, n.d., undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Thomas Pride, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, H.L. Prossler, 1982-1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe Queenan, 1981-1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Ruthellen Quillen, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe Raffa, 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Ramirez, Orlando, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, V.V. Rankine, n.d., undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Rochelle Ratner, 1980-1983 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Shannon Ravenel, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, David Ray, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Ready, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Liam Rector, 1981-1984 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Joel Redon, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, F.D. Reeve, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Mark Reeve, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Bruce D. Reeves, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, William Grove Reid, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Dona Rennick, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Joyce Renwick, 1978-1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Suzanne Ress, 1982-1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Ben Reynolds, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Suzanne Rhodenbaugh, 1980-1987 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeff Richards, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Elliot Richman, 1985-1990 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Steve Richmond, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Kevin Ring, 1979-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, George Riser, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Elisavietta Ritchie, 1978-1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Robinson, John, 1978-1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Andy Robson, 1978-1990 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Rochette Crawley, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Timothy Rodriguez, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Edward Roditi, 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Steven B. Rogers, 1982-1989 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Christine C. Rom, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Steve Romagnoli, 1984-1990 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, C. (Rush Charlie) Romney Brown, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Leon Rooke, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Francis Coleman Rosenberger, 1978-1982 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Kim Rosenfield, nd, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Phyllis Rosenzweig, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Joe Ross, 1982-1991 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, Ross, Robert, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Henry R. Roth, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Anne Rouse, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Lisa Ruffolo, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, John Rothfork, 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Stephanie Rowden, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Steve Ruhl, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, William F. Ryan, 1981-1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Author Correspondence, John Rybicki, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Author Correspondence, Rolf Rykken, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Author Correspondence, Patrick Saari, 1976-1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Author Correspondence, Sy Safransky, 1979-1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Author Correspondence, Miriam Sagan, 1981-1989 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Author Correspondence, Kris Saknussem Johnson, 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Author Correspondence, Jerome Sala, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Author Correspondence, Rachel Salazar, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Author Correspondence, Christy Sheffield Sanford, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Author Correspondence, Ben Satterfield, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Author Correspondence, Joel Sattler, 1979-1988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Author Correspondence, Jack Saunders, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Author Correspondence, Lynne Savitt, 1981-1988 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeanne Schinto, 1983-1989 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Author Correspondence, Lynn Schmidt, 1987-1991 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Author Correspondence, Harold Schneider, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Author Correspondence, P. Schneidre, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Author Correspondence, Jurgen Schoneich, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Author Correspondence, Susan Schultz, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert Scottelaro, 1980-1983 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Author Correspondence, Hart Seely, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Author Correspondence, Deborah Seyler, 1982-1986 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Author Correspondence, Gregg Shapiro, 1985-1989 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Author Correspondence, Catherine Harnett Shaw, nd, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Author Correspondence, Connie Sheldon, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Author Correspondence, Robert G. Sheppard, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Author Correspondence, David Sheridan, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Author Correspondence, Lonnie Sherman, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Author Correspondence, Donna Sherrill, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Author Correspondence, Rita Signorelli Pappas, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Author Correspondence, Jeffrey Skeate, 1980-1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Author Correspondence, Don Skiles, 1982-1990 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Author Correspondence, Morty Sklar, 1979-1989 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Author Correspondence, Mary Lynn Skutley, nd, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Author Correspondence, Anne Marie Skye, 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)